barwa.com.qa 2018-05-31

# Barwa - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to BARWA. This statement discloses the information practices for BARWA Web sites, including what type of information is gathered and tracked, how the information is used, and with whom the information is shared.

We have implemented these practices for the BARWA website (www.BAWRA.com.qa). We have instructed our web-masters to include information on these privacy practices wherever personal​​ information is collected on a BARWA Website.

#### Personal information

In general, you can visit BARWA on the Web without telling us who you are and without revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we or our partners may need information from you.

You may choose to give us personal information, such as your name and address or e-mail id that may be needed, for example, to correspond with you, to process an order or to provide you with a subscription. It is our intent to let you know how we will use such information before we collect it from you on the Internet. We provide this information through the PRIVACY link, which is presented wherever personal information is collected. If you tell us that you do not want us to use this information as basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes.

#### Information security and quality

We intend to protect the quality and integrity of your personally identifiable information. We are implementing appropriate technical and organizational measures, such as using encryption for transmission of credit card numbers, to help us keep your information secure, accurate, current, and complete.

We will make a sincere effort to respond in a timely manner to your requests to correct inaccuracies in your personal information. To correct inaccuracies in your personal information please return the message containing the inaccuracies to the sender with details of the correction requested.

#### Online advertising

BARWA has certain companies help us deliver our banner ads and other online communications. These companies may collect and use information about customers to help us better understand the offers, promotions, and types of advertising that are most appealing to our customers. The information they collect is aggregated so it is not identifiable to a specific individual.

#### Children's data

While none of BARWA's web sites are directed towards children, we are committed to comply with applicable laws and requirements, such as the United States' Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA).

#### Privacy technology

Technology will increasingly help you to have more control over your personal information. It will also help organizations to manage their privacy practices and policies. As an information technology provider, BARWA actively supports the development of privacy technologies to help achieve these goals, and to help create greater trust and confidence in the way personal information is handled. Products and services are available which can help give you privacy protection while navigating the Web.

#### Business relationships

The BARWA site contains links to other Web sites. BARWA is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.​​
